

I'm a result oriented frontend developer with experience in creating Landing Pages and SPA, using React(JS/TS), Redux, HTML & CSS. Now I am improving my skills in this direction and expanding them with new technologies. And also I have interest to learn React Native.

My free time is dedicated to improve my programming skills and boosting my English. After working as a freelancer, I would like to find a project work/full-time job in a creative company with up-to-date task and collaborative team!

Skills

- REACT/REDUX
- JavaScript/TypeScript
- HTML5/CSS3
- AXIOS/REST API
- Unit tests/StoryBook
- MaterialUI
- GIT

Languages

- English Pre-Intermediate (in progress)
- Russian
- Polish (B1)

Contact



@leonid kr



+375 (25) 751-95-35



Belarus, Minsk

LEONID KRUCHENOK

FRONT-END DEVELOPER









Education History

IT-INCUBATOR

Front-end developer | React & Redux

- 2021 2022
- React, Redux, Typescript, REST, Git, Team development ...

HTML ACADEMY, 2020

 JavaScript for begginers, HTML and CSS for begginers

IPK RIPO COLLEGE

Industrial and civil construction

• 2014- 2018 | Builder Technician

Work Experience

FREELANCE

Front-end developer | Dec 2021 - present

Took part in creating learning app, developed login page, modal windows, tests, menu and design. Use next deleloper technologies: React/Redux / ReduxThunk/RestApi/Axios/ReduxForm/Fo rmik /MaterialUI/SCSS, etc. Use TypeScript for best control of the code in work.

INDIVIDUAL ENTREPRENEUR

Create targeted advertising on Instagram & Facebook | 2018 - Dec. 2021

- Communication with customers
- Create ads in social networks
- Development of promotion strategies